<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-09-06T01:58:43-05:00</updated><id>https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/feed.xml</id><title type="html">fastpages</title><subtitle>An easy to use blogging platform with support for Jupyter Notebooks.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Title</title><link href="https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/2022/09/05/ticket2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Title" /><published>2022-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-09-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/2022/09/05/ticket2</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ec Reflection</title><link href="https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/2022/08/29/ec-reflection.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ec Reflection" /><published>2022-08-29T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/2022/08/29/ec-reflection</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the event, I learned a ton about the challenges that come with pursuing computer science. I learned that most people have unique experiences, and that Mr.M’s class is a splendid introduction to the many ideas, and it helps build a solid foundation for the future. I learned about the experiences people go through in college with computer science and the many beneficial aspects the subject has. I learned about the many different unique applications for computer science in many different fields. This makes the major very versatile and has many different directions it can take as they develop. I also was surprised about the major difference between CS at our school and in college, as one of the alumni pointed out the experience in college also is very different in the sense the problems are unique and require a different way to think. I also know understand now that most internships are looking for hard work and problem-solving rather than someone who know all the syntax as that is not as important as problems become more difficult, so logic is the main benefactor of a person. I learned about the use of project base learning and the relevance it has in college and in the industry. I learned that people continue working in project form to develop their learning. Another part of college that is not in our PBL system is a fair amount of tests. I also learned about the different teacher relationship in college, by nature of the college classes professors do not care as much because they have 200 students per class making each student responsible for their own work. This makes a great opportunity in this class as I can get a good amount of attention to improve my coding skills. I was also reminded about the use of computer science in other fields and how it can increase an individual’s worth at a company or organization because it is a very valuable skill. Even in school subjects such as math, computer science can help a ton with understanding the applications for those topics. Working hard is a necessity in computer science as the subjects are not easy and require time, effort and passion. Reputation building is very important, as many professors can be assets in the future as references.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bash Installation Checks</title><link href="https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/jupyter/bash/2022/08/28/bash-tests.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bash Installation Checks" /><published>2022-08-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-08-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/jupyter/bash/2022/08/28/bash-tests</id><author><name></name></author><category term="jupyter" /><category term="bash" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checking that everything is installed]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apel Vocab</title><link href="https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/2022/08/28/apel-vocab.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apel Vocab" /><published>2022-08-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-08-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/2022/08/28/apel-vocab</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terms to know - Rhetorical Devices]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Python Notebook</title><link href="https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/jupyter/python/2022/08/28/quizzes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Python Notebook" /><published>2022-08-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-08-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://somaditya1.github.io/fastpages-csa/jupyter/python/2022/08/28/quizzes</id><author><name></name></author><category term="jupyter" /><category term="python" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python test code]]></summary></entry></feed>